

Yang, Bo

Developer



+1-415-420-9693



https://yang-bo.com



yang-bo@yang-bo.com



pop_atry



yang_bo



955091



Atry

About me -

I am a developer who knows how to create application frameworks.

I founded a number of open-source projects for creating micro-services, neural networks, reactive GUIs, and DSLs, which are stared 3000+ times on GitHub.

My current interests include machine learning infrastructure and the application of functional programming languages to real-world problems.

Skills —

Scala

Machine Learning

Software Design

Agile Project Management

Hack *5.5 Haxe *5.5 OpenCL *5
DevOps *5 ActionScript *4
C++ *4 Java *4 JavaScript *4
Rust *4 OCaml *4 Testing *3
C *3 Spark *3 Akka *3

(*)[The skill scale is from 0 (Fundamental Awareness) to 6 (Expert).]

Experience

	Experien	ce			
	2023-	Preemo Inc Machi As Preemo's only MLE, I conceptualized multitenancy service fererence, and developed the whole API service from scratch https://gradient.ai, except for billing and authentication module	h, sonely, known as		
	2019-2022	Meta Platforms Inc I built machine learning infrastructure to detect payment fraud a variety of products. Then I joined the Hack/HHVM OSS team, v of maintaining HHVM's open-source branch.	the Hack/HHVM OSS team, where I was in charge		
	2015-2019	Thoughtworks Inc Senior Consulta I maintained a number of open-source projects sponsored by The Tech Lead, delivered various projects of mobile, web applications			
	2014	Shenzhen QiFun Network Corp., LTD I led the Q-Force Team in developing a game engine along with two mobile games.	Tech Lead its related tools, and		
	2011-2013	Shenzhen Putaoteng Network Technology Co., Ltd. I led the start-up team in developing a 3D side-scrolling game en social game Nan Da Nu Pei.	Co-founder gine VinyHome and a		
	2008-2011	NetEase, Inc. I participated in various product teams as a developer or the tring Zhan Guo Feng Yun (web game), Ka Pai Dui Jue (web game) engine).			
	2007	Beijing HiPiHi Information Technology Corp.,Ltd developed in the both server-side and client-side of the 3D virtual	Software Engineer al world, HiPiHi World.		
	2006-2007	Beijing AutoNavi Software Co., Ltd. As a developer, I developed some components for a 3D navigation	Software Engineer on software.		
	Open-sou	urce projects			
	2021-2022	HHVM is Meta's virtual machine to run Hack. I ported the open source NixOS and created CI pipeline for building, testing, and packaging.	C++/Rust/OCaml e branch of HHVM to ng HHVM.		
	since 2018	Dsl.scala is a framework to extend Scala language features in libraries. I al work to Haskell as Control.Dsl.	Scala so ported this frame-		
	since 2016	DeepLearning.scala and Compute.scala are libraries for creating complex neural networks.	Scala		
	since 2015	Binding.scala is a reactive templating language for creating web and desktop (Scala GUI.		
	2015-2016	Microbuilder Haxe / Sca is a toolkit to build system across micro-services implemented communicating via RESTful JSON API.	la / Java / JavaScript in various languages		
	since 2012	haxe-continuation provides async/await syntax for Haxe.	Haxe		
	since 2010	protoc-gen-as3 is a Protocol Buffers plugin for ActionScript 3.	ActionScript3		
	since 2007	other 100+ of open-source projects			
Publications					
	2017	Mondic Deep Learning	first author		

2017 2017 2009 Talks	Mondic Deep Learning Ad-hoc polymorphic delimited continuations Adobe Flex 3: Training from the Source	first author first author translator
2017 2017	Deeplearning.scala - Thoughts and practices on OSS AI framework Monadic Deep Learning	DBTC Strange Loop

ArchData Summit · Beijing

QCon · Beijing

ECUG Con

Education

2017

2016

2015

2002-2006 Southwest University of Political Science and Law Bachelor Of Laws

Specific-domain extension in an universal language

Neural Networks & Functional Programming

More than Async